{
	"data": [
    {
      "question": "We never listen to Beethoven without ___.",
      "a": "being deeply impressed",
      "b": "impressing deeply",
      "c": "having deeply impressed",
      "d": "to be deeply impressed",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n- Without + Verb_ing: Not doing sth \n- Verb is passive voice",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "42",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "___ no persuading him to buy the car.",
      "a": "There was",
      "b": "It was",
      "c": "Here was",
      "d": "That was",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n- There + be: means \"have\"",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "42",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "He repented _________ idle in his youth.",
      "a": "of being",
      "b": "of having been",
      "c": "to be",
      "d": "to have been",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n\n- Repent + V_ing: regret of something/ not doing something\n\n- Verb tense is perfect tense",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "42",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Don't forget ___ to me. Let's keep in touch.",
      "a": "to write",
      "b": "writing",
      "c": "having written",
      "d": "to have written",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n\n- Forget + V_ing: Forget something which have already happened/done\n\n- Forget+  To Verb: Forget To do something\n\n- Forget + V_ing: Forget something which have already happened/done\n\n- Forget+  To Verb: Forget To do something\n\n",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "42",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Being easy to break, the article wants ___.",
      "a": "carefully to handle",
      "b": "careful handling",
      "c": "to handle with care",
      "d": "for careful handling",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n\n- Want + To be Past Particple/ V_ing: if before \"want\" is not person\n\n- Want + To Verb:  If before \"want\" is person",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "42",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is no use ___ to deceive her.",
      "a": "try",
      "b": "tried",
      "c": "trying",
      "d": "being tried",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n\n- No use V_ing:  it is hopeless to do something; it is pointless to do something\n\n- This is active voice: the answer \"being tried\" is not correct.",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "42",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Unless you both stop ___, I will call in the police.",
      "a": "fighting",
      "b": "to fight",
      "c": "having fought",
      "d": "being fought",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n- Stop + V_ing: no longer doing something \n- Stop + To Verb: stop (doing) something to do something ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "42",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "On _________ our village, we asked him for chocolate.",
      "a": "him to reach",
      "b": "his to reach",
      "c": "for him to reach",
      "d": "his reaching",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- Base on structure, missing word should be a noun phrase",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "42",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "An old friend of mine came near ___ by the train.",
      "a": "to kill",
      "b": "killing",
      "c": "being killed",
      "d": "to being killing",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n\n- Use Verb-ing  when two things happen at the same time.\n\n- When one action happens during another action, use Verb_ing for longer action\n\n- Passive voice",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "42",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "There is no ___ the fact that he was innocent.",
      "a": "to deny",
      "b": "denying",
      "c": "being denied",
      "d": "denial",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n\n- There is no denying: something is true because it's a (proven) fact\n\n",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "42",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    }
  ]
}